终空     前情提要
【家长提示】本片的评级为 TV-14-DLV，
可能包含暗示性对话、粗俗语言和暴力等内容，
因而不建议 14 岁以下儿童独自观赏。
盖瑞和阿瓦卡多陷入了生死危机
Gary and Avocato got their butt cheeks in a hot vise.
“总司令”正在步步紧逼他们  妈呀！
The Lord Commander is hot on their trail. Oh, crap!
如今  我们的两位大英雄开始合作
Now our heroes have joined forces
保护月饼  并且拯救阿瓦卡多的儿子  小卡多
to protect Mooncake and save Avocato's son, Little Cato.
他们会怎样做呢？又会藏身何处呢？
What are they going to do? Where are they going to hide?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
所以大家一起来看今天的这一集吧
That's why we're watching this episode, y'all!
你的氧气还够用7分钟  盖瑞
You have 7 minutes of oxygen left, Gary.
HUE  瞧  卡尔在那边
HUE, look, it's Carl.
卡尔  咋样啊？
Carl, how's life?
卡尔已经死了  盖瑞
Carl is dead, Gary.
活该  卡尔
Classic Carl.
那混蛋还欠我25刀呢
That bastard owes me 25 bucks.
紧急求救！紧急求救！
Mayday, mayday!
可以去一下噪音吗  HUE？
Can you clean that up, HUE?
我试试看
I can try.
我们光折时受到了干扰！
[We lightfolded into scramble!]
信号干扰有点儿严重
There is quite a bit of interference.
我们需要帮助！
We need help!
知道那个人是谁吗？
Any idea who it is?
不要啊！一个人都没有吗？
No! Is anyone out there?
不知道  盖瑞  认不出来
No, Gary. I'm afraid not.
要不  我去帮帮他…
Well, maybe I can help these --
算了  我还是在这里歇一会吧
Actually, I'll just chill over here.
Translated by @SerCom_KC
OPEN TRANSLATION PROJECT
给你的
For you!
你会用到的
This will help.
翻译版本
v1.0.0-CHS
这是什么东西
What is this?
你是谁？
Who's there?
翻译
SerCom_KC
你的父亲就是个懦夫
Your father is a coward!
校对
万俟猫
父亲一定会来救我的
My father will come for me,
校对
呱呱鴨
他也一定会杀了你
and he will kill you
校对
旗木佐罗
除非你已经死在我的手下
if I don't first.
Yah!
Ow.
时间轴
SerCom_KC
奎恩  我看起来是不是有些不一样？
Quinn, do I look any different?
特效
SerCom_KC
不一样对吧  因为你面前正是全银河通缉度最高的男人
I should because you're looking at the most wanted man in the galaxy.
喔  瞧瞧谁来了
Oh, look who it is.
阿瓦卡多  来跟奎恩打个招呼
Avocato, come say hi to Quinn.
不要
No.
他脾气不太好
He's a bit of a grouch,
不过这跟他儿子被绑架有关
but his son has been kidnapped.
是啊  我懂
Yeah. I know.
总之  重大进展  我有机械臂了
Anyways, big development. I have a robot arm.
你看
Look at this!
妈呀  怎么把它…
Oh, my god! How do I...
今天就先到这里吧
I think that's all I have for you today.
翻译项目地址
translatedby.sercomkc.org/finalspace
给我打电话喔  奎恩
Give me a call, Quinn.
本翻译作品按照CC BY-NC-SA 4.0许可协议向公众授权
未经授权禁止用于任何商业用途
噢  忘记说了  再过四天  我就自由了
Oh, I almost forgot. In four days, I'm a free man.
到那个时候  你有什么打…
What do you say when I turn...
迫近警告  迫近警告
Proximity alert. Proximity alert.
盖瑞  我们正在遭受“总司令”重型焚化炉的袭击
Gary, we are taking fire from the Lord Commander's heavy incinerators.
抓紧了  怎么办  HUE？
Grab it firm. What do we do, HUE?
计算中  检测到附近有入侵现象
Calculating. I am detecting an incursion in our proximity.
有啥？
A what?
有时虫  盖瑞
A temporal worm, Gary.
这是你唯一的选择
It's your only option.
时虫可能会把我们送到几千年前或几千年后  盖瑞
A temporal worm could send us backwards or forwards thousands of years in time, Gary.
你确定我们只能选这条路吗？
Are you sure that's the only choice we have?
带我们进去
Feed us to it!
Whoa!
Aah!
嗯  屁股真翘
Mm, pressed hams.
真是屌爆了！
That was wondrous!
屌爆了就遮一下好吗  天啊
How about covering up that dick situation you've got going there? Jeez.
时间刚刚好
In good time.
话说回来  现在是什么时候？
Speaking of which, when are we?
现在你高兴了吧
Happy?
盖瑞  我们穿越到了四天后
Gary, we have jumped four days into the future.
等等  你说啥？
Wait. What?
也就是说我最后的四天刑期已经过完了  对吧  HUE？
That means my last four days of jail are up. Right, HUE?
芝麻开门  宝藏速来
Open sesame! Unlock my bounty!
根据第九条规定
Clause nine of your imprisonment
在押期间  所有时间相关的干扰对你的刑期无影响
stipulates that all time-related disruptions have zero effect on your sentence.
啥？没有巧克力味的大金币吗？
What? So no chocolate treasure coins?
你指的是饼干吗  盖瑞？
Are you referring to cookies, Gary?
对啊
Yes!
哦  那就没有了
Oh, then no.
你这是在抬价  HUE  抬价啊！
This is a load, HUE, a load!
听着  盖瑞  我们已经被盯上了
Listen, Gary. We're marked targets,
无论我们藏到哪个洞里
and no matter what hole we hide in,
都能被“总司令”洞察
the Lord Commander will find us in our hole
月饼就会被他从洞里带走
and take Mooncake from that hole.
我知道这听起来有点空洞
I know that's a whole lot of holes,
但我们现在真的进了一个无底洞了
but we're in a whole lot of trouble.
HUE？
HUE?
正如阿瓦卡多所说
Avocato is correct.
在确定下一步做什么之前  我们必须把他藏起来
We need to hide him until we figure things out.
我知道一个收留逃犯的地方
Look. I've heard of a place that safeguards fugitives.
离我们最近的一个在雅尔诺星
The closest one is on Yarno.
只要在那里  没人能发现他
No one will find him there.
HUE  让引擎加速
HUE, spool up the engines.
我们就去雅尔诺星
We're going to Yarno.
兆压     18650区
十二教团
胡拉助手  我一直很敬重十二教团
Helper Hula, I've always respected the Order of the Twelve
作为全宇宙观察者的地位
being the eyes of the universe.
E-351在哪里？
Where is E-351?
啊  你命不久矣
Ah! You're dying!
命不久矣？是吗  大天才
Dying? Really, genius?
我知道我快死了！
I know I'm dying!
每使用一次那个“光线”
Every time you use your light,
你就离死亡更近了一步
you quicken your own death.
所以我才需要月饼
That's why I need Mooncake,
那个笨蛋好像是这么叫的吧
or whatever that idiot calls him.
我需要他才能活下去  告诉我他在哪里
I need him to live. Tell me where he is.
耐心
Patience.
你这算助人吗
That wasn't very helpful.
Ugh!
帮我找到他
You will find him for me,
否则下次就别怪我不客气了
or next time I finish the job.
雅尔诺星
哈佬  我是扎尔贡·图卡历什
Gworplo! I'm Zargon Tukalishi,
欢迎来到雅尔…
and welcome to Yarn--
死亡收割祭快开始啦
I can't wait for Deathcropolis!
看来最近这里发生了一些变化呢
Looks like they've made some changes around here.
你还真别说  这死亡收割祭听上去
You don't say, because the Deathcropolis
就好像温馨的教会野餐一样
just sounded like a lovely church picnic.
不用担心  月饼
Don't worry, Mooncake.
有我们在呢
We got this.
穆诺团子  自产的穆诺团子
Moonobumps, homemade moonobumps.
哇  不错啊  居然还有免费送糖的
Oh, sweet! They're just handing out free candy!
Wow. Whoa.
Oh, oh,
他手上有根棒冰欸
he has a popsicle now!
Ahh!
简直恍若隔世啊
I feel so replenished.
天啊
Oh, wow.
哇  啥东西啊？
Oh! Just what is this?
我的奶子上怎么有只飞镖
There's a dart sticking out of my chesticles!
能不能不要从奇葩外星人手里乱拿东西？
Can you not take crap from weird alien skeevoids?
好的  “不要从奇葩手里乱拿东西”
Noted, "Do not take crap from skeevoids."
Ugh.
Ahh!
距离木星2秒差距的地方
There's a quantum gravitational disturbance emanating
涌出了量子引力干扰
two parsecs from Jupiter.
如果我的计算正确  所有的生命都会…
If my math is right, all our lives might depend --
奎恩  我是三烦
Quinn, it's Tribore.
不用担心我  我在你的房间里
Don't worry. I'm at your place.
目前一切正常  但我有个非常坏的消息
Everything is okay, but super bad news.
你不会喜欢听的
You're not going to like it.
说实在的  我也不知道这年头喜欢怎么了
In fact, I don't know what happened to all the like.
喜欢都到哪里去了？
Where did all the like go?
有话快说
Tell me, already!
我会有话快说的
I will tell you, already.
就在昨天  斯通长官派遣了一艘绝统巡航船前来逮捕你
Superior Stone dispatched an Imperium cruiser yesterday to apprehend you
据说你违反了多条法令  差不多47条
because you kind of broke a lot of laws, like 47 laws.
为什么不早点告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
为什么不早点告诉你呢？
Why didn't I tell you sooner?
这是个问题  对吧？
That is the question, isn't it?
回答  我最近很忙
The answer, I've been busy.
你这是在动我的的东西吗？
Are you touching my stuff?
为什么我要动你的东西呢
Why would I be touching your stuff.
这些会让我看起来又梦幻又漂亮的东西
that makes me look so dreamy and beautiful.
我是绝对不会碰你那些漂亮的东西的
I would never be touching your beautiful stuff.
奎恩  一艘绝统巡航船正在靠近
Quinn, an Imperium cruiser is closing in on your position.
就是这里  盖瑞
This is the place, Gary.
就是这里？
This is the place?
那个地方就是“这里”？
This, right here, is the place?
我是不会下去的
I'm not going down there.
朋友  欢迎来到十二教团雅尔诺支部
Welcome, friends, to the Order of Twelve Yarno chapter.
我们的代表很快就会来接见你
A representative will meet you shortly.
请问我有什么可以…
How can I --
妈呀
Jeez!
帮到你的吗？
...help?
被你吓到了
You got me.
你是助手吗？
Are you a Helper?
喔  不是的
Oh, no.
我只协助助手的工作
I assist the Helpers.
那你就是助手的助手咯？
So you're a Helper-helper?
我会告诉他  你们已经…
I will tell him you have...
到了
arrived.
那个家伙直接穿墙消失了
Guy straight up ghosted through that wall.
接受事实吧
Live with it.
做不到啊
I can't.
那个家伙  居然直接穿墙消失了啊
The guy just ghosted through that wall, yo.
Ahh!
请问你需要什么帮助吗？
How can I help?
我们乐于助人
We love to help.
谢谢
Thanks.
是这样的  我们需要给这个小家伙找个安全的地方
Uh... well, we need to find a safe place for my little buddy.
抱歉  我们已经满员了
Sorry. We're at capacity.
Oh!
不过再挤一个房间还是没问题的
But we could always squeeze in one more.
如此珍贵的样本
Such a precious specimen.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
你…你能不要用那么瘆人的语气行吗？
C-can you say that just a little less creepy-like?
好吧  看来不行
Okay. I guess not.
月饼啊
Mooncake.
Chookity?
我不是说要就此分别  知道吗？
No one's saying goodbye here. Okay?
我会尽快赶回来的
I'll be back as soon as I can.
就这一小段时间  我保证
It's only temporary. I promise.
Chookity pok.
盖瑞  他不会有事的
Gary, he'll be fine.
他能自己照顾自己
He can take care of himself.
对了先生  我还没问过你的名字呢  叫…
By the way, I never got your name, mister...
史蒂佛
Stevil.
Stevil
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
停一下
Pump the breaks.
好吧  这个怪胎从名字开始就带着邪恶
Okay. The freaking guy has evil in his name.
evil
我他妈是不会把月饼交给一个叫做史蒂佛的家伙的！
I'm not handing Mooncake over to a guy freaking named Stevil!
史蒂佛的确有点可疑
Stevil is a bit alarming.
就是有点可疑！
It is a bit alarming!
我们只是想助人而已
We only want to help!
阿瓦卡多  我们换个地方吧
Avocato, let's find another place.
走了
Let's go.
休想！
Stop!
好吧
Okay.
这下完全是班西哭号级别的可疑了
This is full-blown banshee screech, alarming!
※班西（banshee）是爱尔兰神话中的报丧女妖。根据传说，班西会在某人将要死去的时候开始哭号。
月饼！
Mooncake!
沉睡吧
Sleep.
通知高阶助手胡拉  我们已经全力协助了
Alert High Helper Hula we have been most helpful.
史蒂佛真是邪恶到名字上了！
Stevil lived right up to the evil in his name!
现在我们还进了这个超安全的昏厥游乐园
Look! We made it to the super safe oblivion amusement park
全是连绵不绝的危险楼梯
of never-ending unsafe stairs!
我好开心啊  真是谢谢了  阿瓦卡多
What fun! Thanks, Avocato.
这是拉撒路陷阱
It's a Lazarus trap.
做这个的人肯定是陷阱大师
Only master trap-makers can make these,
搞不好还是个特别喜欢楼梯的人
and people who really like stairs.
起码我们还没有陷进岩浆池之类的
At least we're not sinking into, like, a lake of lava or something.
听我说  我们想象的一切都会变成现实  懂吗？
Listen to me. Anything we think of becomes reality. Okay?
好的  那我们就想开一点
Right. Okay. So we've got to think positive.
喔  喔  饼干！
Ooh, ooh! Cookies!
不要啊
No!
Hey!
吃了我吧  我超好吃  我是一片饼干
Eat me! I'm delicious! I'm a cookie!
怎么啦  我又没想什么凶残的杀人零食
What? It's not like I'm imagining murderous killing confections?
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
大家都…很期待今天的死亡收割祭上…谁会死
Everybody is super excited about today's sacrifices at the Deathcropolis.
Ooh!
但你是不会死的
But you're not being sacrificed.
“总司令”需要你
The Lord Commander needs you.
他在干啥？
What is he doing?
Chookity pok!
奎恩·艾冈  我们奉命以偷窃航空器材的重大罪名逮捕你
Quinn Airgon, we have orders to arrest you for aerial grand theft.
查克？
Chuck?
没错  我是查克
Yes. This is Chuck.
立即投降  这样我们还能放你一马
Now, please surrender, and this all goes away.
听着  死脑残  我拒绝
Listen, jerk nuts. No.
她是不是骂了我死脑残？
Did she just call me jerk nuts?
哦  好吧  行  行
Oh. Okay, yeah. Yeah.
那你就接受逮捕吧
I think you are under arrest.
喂  王八蛋  想都别想
Hey! Douche canoe, not happening.
天啊  居然说我王八蛋
God. You said, "Douche canoe."
行啊  听好了  奎恩
All right. Listen, Quinn.
不  你给我听好了
No. You listen.
我现在可是在拯救世界
I'm trying to save the world, here.
请你立马调转方向
So you're going to turn your vessel around
就当作你没看到我
and forget you ever saw me.
老兄  你哭了？
Dude, are you crying?
没有  没有  我没哭
No. No, I'm not crying.
只是太空花粉而已
It's space pollen.
绝统干预
啊呀呀  你没念急急如律令
Ah, ah, ah! Didn't say the magic word!
啊  为啥饼干全跳到我身上了啊
Aaah! Why am I the only one covered in cookies?
你就没…啊  啊！
You have not -- ah, ah!
盖瑞  不要再想饼干了
Gary, de-think the cookies!
恐怕我做不到  我想象力太丰富了
Not sure that's possible. I'm a very creative guy.
这些饼干要是有激光眼岂不是逆天了
Like, wouldn't it be cool if they had, like, laser eyes?
啊  快跑啊
Aah! Run!
我的妈呀  不要啊  不要啊
Oh, my God! No! No!
快想点别的东西
Think of something else.
什么都好！
Anything else!
啥  三叉戟吗？
What, like tridents?
别啊
No!
好棒啊
Yeah!
太棒了
Yes!
别啊  别想什么三叉戟啊！
No! Not like tridents!
我脑子里全是会用三叉戟又有激光眼的死亡小饼干啊
I'm thinking about little trident-wielding laser-shooting death cookies!
我啥都没想  没想  没想
I'm thinking of nothing, nothing, nothing.
Oh! Whoa!
啊  天啊
Oh! Oh, my gosh.
我要把你的眼珠子吃掉
I'm going to eat your eyes out.
然后在眼窝里尿尿
And pee in your sockets!
你们是逃不出这个地方的
You're never going to leave this place.
为什么那片饼干会一个人走在边上？
Why is that one cookie lone-wolfing it across the edge?
喔  它开始飞跃了
Oh! He's leaping!
哇  简直就像天使一样
Whoa! He's like an angel!
我的天…
Oh, my God --
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
它在戳我眼珠子啊
It's stabbing my eyes!
Ahh!
Ohh.
Chookity pok!
以死者之名  祝生者长存
To the ones who live for the ones who die!
这一点都不公平  我做了那么多的好事
It's not fair. I've been good.
帮了那么多的人
I help people.
我已经很耐心了  都快要不耐烦了
I've been patient, unbelievably patient!
噢  “总司令”
Oh, Lord Commander!
我把您的药端来了  大人
I-I brought your medicine, sir!
我还在旁边放了一片甜饼
I put a little biscuit on the side,
都是为了您  我无上的小王子
just for you, my special little prince.
这些都是什么东西
What is this?
Ugh! Gah!
我喜欢的是更小一点的甜饼
I like the much littler kind of biscuits.
我已经跟你说过了  埃里克
I have told you this, Eric.
我已经说过了！
I told you this!
我们已经全力协助了
We have been most helpful.
我们找到了月饼
We have found Mooncake.
我的耐心终于有了回报
My patience paid off.
杀戮吧
The more you kill,
十二泰坦会愈加开心的
the more the Twelve Titans beyond rejoice.
Ahh!
盖瑞  我们必须醒过来
Gary, we need to wake up.
把眼睛闭上
Close your eyes.
又让我醒来  又让我闭上眼睛？
You want me to wake up by closing my eyes?
这根本说不通啊
That doesn't make any sense!
在这里没有哪件事是说得通的
Nothing makes any sense in here!
好吧  有道理
All right. Good point.
好吧  闭上眼睛
Okay. I'm closing my eyes.
根本没用
It's not working.
嗨  盖瑞
Hi, Gary.
奎恩？
Quinn?
好久不见
It's been a long time.
快点过来  我好想你
Come here. I missed you.
真的…是你吗？
Is it... really you?
再靠近一点
Closer.
盖瑞…
Gary...
别拦着我！
Get off me!
这也是陷阱
It's part of the trap.
盖瑞  别听他说的
Gary, don't listen to him.
你要相信我  她并不是真的在那里
You need to trust me. She isn't real.
我们能回家了吗  爸爸？
Are we going home, dad?
相信我  伙计  我们两个都要醒过来
Trust me, buddy. We both need to wake up.
我不想再醒来了
I don't want to wake up.
那就只好请你忍一忍了
Then you're really not going to want this.
我们出来了  是我救的我们
We're out! I saved us.
不对  明明是我救的你
No, I saved you.
而我也救了你
And I, you.
你并没有救我
No, you didn't.
但我的确救了你啊
But I did.
你差点就把我们害死了  盖瑞
You almost got us killed, Gary.
那我们两个就扯平了
Then we're even.
赶紧去找月饼！
We've got to find Mooncake!
盖瑞  我说了  月饼不会有事的
Gary, I told you Mooncake is going to be okay.
他可是超级武器
He's a super weapon.
才不对！
Wrong!
我的小绿球朋友可是人畜无害  充满爱的口香糖球
Little green ball friend is a harmless gumball of love!
HUE  在吗？
HUE, you there?
你去哪里了  盖瑞？
Where have you been, Gary?
要解释的话估计你会觉得我疯了
It would sound too insane to even explain.
你能帮我锁定一下月饼的位置吗？
Can you lock into Mooncake's location?
呃  盖瑞？
Uh, Gary?
小家伙
Little buddy.
最后的献祭者即将揭晓
The final sacrifice awaits.
杀！杀！杀！杀！
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
你好呀  月饼
Hello, Mooncake.
我可是找了你好久了
I have been looking all over for you.
别害羞嘛
Don't be shy.
过来打个招呼啊
Come in and say hello.
Ahh!
为什么我会变得这么虚弱？
How did I become so weak?
月饼！
Mooncake!
Doot, doot, doot, doot!
Chookity!
Oh!
盖瑞！
Gary!
是时候收手了  “那个”盖瑞
It's over, The Gary.
是盖瑞  我就叫盖瑞
"Gary." It's just "Gary."
你到底想干什么  老兄？
What is your deal, dude?
为啥要死缠着我们不放？
Why won't you just leave us alone?
看来你什么都不知道啊
You have no idea, do you?
月饼就是钥匙
Mooncake is the key.
这个生命体将会打开
That being can unlock
通往“终空”的大门
Final Space.
“终空”又它娘的是啥鬼？
What the mother-loving crap is Final Space?
不关你事
That's my business.
你是想跟我玩游戏吗  盖瑞？
Should we play a game, Gary?
我最喜欢游戏了  而且胜利的永远是我
I love games. I always win.
你知道我的要求  所以我…
You know what I want, and I --
Ya!
我  的  天  啊
Oh, my gosh!
饿地神啊
Sweet Grandor's glove!
你真的是能毁灭行星的超级武器！
You are a planet-destroying super weapon!
Chookity!
哇  太棒了
Whoa! Yes!
真是太他妈的刺激了
That's so freaking tight!
游戏哪有像你这么玩的
That's not how we play the game!
那  这个游戏如何？
How about this game?
哈  没打中吧
Ah, you missed.
干
Freak.
瞄准门锁！
Shoot for the locks!
盖瑞  小心！
Gary, look out!
Ugh!
Ah!
Ugh.
我来救你啦  盖瑞
I'm going to save you, Gary!
我在救你喔
I'm saving you!
我是来救你的  盖瑞
I'm here to save you, Gary!
我拯救世界啦
The day is saved.
妈的KVN  我恨死你了
Freaking KVN! I hate you so much!
你给我早点去死吧
I truly can't wait for the day you die!
我的妈  没人会感到悲伤
Oh, my gosh. No one will be sad.
只会有满满的幸福感
There will only be happiness!
嘿  盖瑞
Hey, Gary!
想都别想  绝对想都别想
Don't even. Just don't even.
KVN拯救了一切
KVN has saved everything.
如此巨大的量子引力干扰  居然还在扩散
The gravitational disturbance, it's massive and growing -- a lot...
而且是飞速扩散啊
a lot, a lot.
我说的就是这个意思啊
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
探针即将失控  探针即将失控
Probe failure imminent. Probe failure imminent.
我们必须马上离开这里
We need to get out of here right now.
上帝啊  启动后推进器
Oh, God! Engage rear thrusters!
Ahh!
Ah!
我不是王八蛋啊
I am not a douche canoe!
Ahh!
求救  求救  我是奎恩·艾冈
Mayday, mayday! This is Quinn Airgon!
有人听得到吗？救命啊！
Can someone hear me? Help me!
我按你的要求  把所有转出兆压的犯人全部扫描了一遍
I've processed your scan of all prisoner transfers out of Tera Con Prime.
没有发现小卡多
There is no match for Little Cato.
月饼？
Mooncake?
怎么了  伙计？
What's wrong, bud?
Mm.
我知道了
I get it.
也就是说  你能在脸上开个孔  射出死亡光线
So you shoot a murder beam out of your face hole.
这有什么
So what?
你可是我们中间最厉害的一个欸
I mean, it happens to the best of us.
就像有一天  我吃了一个卷饼
I mean, just the other day I had a burrito,
然后你应该看到我射出了他妈的死亡光线
and you should have saw the freaking murder beam
就是从我的…
that came out of my ba--
就  就是说  仔细想想的话
And, you know, it's actually pretty sweet,
其实还挺棒的
if you think about it.
我的意思是  我想让你知道
I mean, I just want you to know that
就算是这样  也不会影响到你和这家伙…
that doesn't change anything between you and this guy.
说我吗？
Me?
不是！
Not you!
Chookity!
…和他的关系
Him.
又不是说你就是坏人了  真的不是
It doesn't make you the bad guy. It really doesn't.
依我看  那个想把你当作武器用的人渣才是坏人
I mean, it makes the scum who want to use you as the weapon the bad guy.
听着  你就是个好人  打心底里就是
Look, you're a good guy to the max core.
Ohh!
我不会再离开你了
I'm never going to let you go again.
我只会把你托付给一个人
I now know the only one I can trust with you
就是最厉害的自己
is my own awesomeness.
Mm!
我感觉我喜欢上这一切了
I'm starting to like these.
Mm.
盖瑞  我收到了一个求救信号
Gary, I am receiving a mayday call.
求救  求救  我是奎恩·艾冈
Mayday, mayday! This is Quinn Airgon!
有人听得到吗？救命啊！
Can someone hear me? Help me!
我的妈
Oh, my crap.
奎恩来了
It's Quinn.